Izzy: Hey! Look out!
Ben: Hi. I have a reservation for four nights.
My name is Ben Fischer.
Izzy: Are you on holiday?
Ben: No. I’m a student.
Izzy: Bye, Mr Fischer.
Ben: Ben…My name’s Ben…Wait, what’s your name?
Andre: Good afternoon, Ben.
Ben: Sorry I’m late.
Andre: The class starts at nine o’clock.
It’s half past nine.
Ben: I’m really sorry.
Andre: Sleeping in class.
Ben: I…Sorry, Andre.
I’m really tired.
Andre: Can I see some of your work?
These are really…
great, Ben.
Yeah, I like these.
Ben: Oh. Thank you.
Andre: These are good too.
But these…are nothing special.
Look, I know it’s difficult,
but I don’t want good photos.
I want great photos.
Ben: OK, Andre.
Andre: My job is to teach you how to take great photos.
More photos like these.
I don’t want photos like these.
Ben: OK. Sure, Andre.
Thanks.
Andre: Go and have a coffee and wake up.